igrezadecu.com 2019-10-08

# Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, feel free to contact us: [ Contact ](https://igrezadecu.com/contact/)

Privacy of igrezadecu.com visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by igrezadecu.com and how it is used. 

By using the Services you agree to observe and be bound by this Privacy Policy and you consent to the processing, collection, use and disclosure of your information and data in accordance with its terms. Please do not use the Services if you do not agree to this Privacy Policy.

#### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, igrezadecu.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

#### Personal Information

We are strongly committed to protecting your privacy online. therefore igrezadecu.com does not request nor collect any personally identifiable information. Your IP address may be used to gather broad demographic information and general visiting paterns. 

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

igrezadecu.com does use cookies exept the cooke that set GDPR consent preferences. 

#### Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons

Some of our analytics and advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include: 

#### Google Analytics

This site uses Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solution on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content.

For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page.

#### DoubleClick

DoubleClick uses cookies to improve advertising. Some common applications are to target advertising based on what’s relevant to a user, to improve reporting on campaign performance, and to avoid showing ads the user has already seen.

The cookie ID in each DoubleClick cookie is essential to these applications. For example, DoubleClick uses cookie IDs to keep a log of which ads show to which browsers. When it’s time to serve an ad to a browser, DoubleClick can use the browser’s cookie ID to check which DoubleClick ads have already been delivered to that particular browser. That’s how DoubleClick avoids showing ads the user has already seen. In the same way, cookie IDs allow DoubleClick to log conversions related to ad requests—such as when a user views a DoubleClick ad and later uses the same browser to visit the advertiser’s website and make a purchase.

DoubleClick cookies contain no personally identifiable information. Sometimes the cookie contains an additional identifier that is similar in appearance to the cookie ID. This identifier is used to identify an ad campaign to which a user was exposed previously; but no personally identifiable information is stored by DoubleClick in the cookie. 

### Opting out

If a user opts out using the [Ads Settings ](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences), the unique DoubleClick cookie ID on the user’s browser is overwritten with the phrase “OPT_OUT”. Because there is no longer a unique cookie ID, the opt-out cookie can’t be associated with a particular browser. 

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on igrezadecu.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to igrezadecu.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following - [ URL ](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  
These third-party analytics and ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on igrezadecu.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

igrezadecu.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. igrezadecu.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

#### Liability

Our policy is to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, followed by valid proof of ownership igrezadecu.com will review and if applicable, disable and remove the games in question.  

#### Proprietary Rights of the Games

Most of the games published on igrezadecu.com are free games, freely available on public domains. Games are submitted or suggested to us by our visitors or their owners/creators. Igrezadecu.com can not confirm if their creators have respected the others intellectual properties or rights. Igrezadecu.com do not claim any ownership of the games or characters, logos and trademarks shown within games. All Trademarks and Copyrights are duly acknowledged as belonging to their lawful owners. Igrezadecu.com is not associated, authorized, endorsed by, or in any way officially connected with copyright and trademark owners of the games featured on igrezadecu.com. 

#### Trademarks, logos and characters

images displayed on igrezadecu.com are screenshots from the games itself, igrezadecu.com is not connected, endorsed or affiliated with trademarks, characters or logos shown within the games or their screenshots. 

#### External Links

igrezadecu.com site contains links to other sites. igrezadecu.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.  
igrezadecu.com does not accept any responsibility about the websites which are linking to our website and the outgoing links in the games published at the website.  

#### Terms of Use

When visiting igrezadecu.com website and/or using its any software, game, you fully agree with it on its "Privacy Policy" and "Terms of Use" conditions. If you do not agree on any of these conditions, you are not allowed to use the website and or its services. igrezadecu.com has the right to update and modify the policies any time. The visitors always should check the related pages to see updates.  

#### Access Restrictions

igrezadecu.com website is suitable the visitors over 13 year age, the younger visitors are suggested to use its service and games together with their parents.
